Contact

48 Thomas Street, The Liberties, Dublin 8 +353834191605 (Mobile) y.m.lima19@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yurilima-40118bb3 (LinkedIn) yurilima.com.br (Personal) github.com/Yuri-Lima (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
C (Programming Language)
Real-Time Operating Systems
(RTOS)

Languages

English (Limited Working)

Certifications

Designing RESTful APIs

FreeRTO's Real-Yime Operating System with ESP32

HTTP Essential Training

NodeMCU ESP8266 - Socket / Server Applications for IOT

Yuri Lima

I'm looking for an opportunity to be a Junior Developer to grow up the knowledge that I've learned with Python and Django. County Dublin

Summary

Skills include embedded, hardware design. Industry experience in embedded C/C++, Python, Linux, MatLab and software version control (GitHub).

I've learned HTML, CSS3, Java Script and SQL.

Experience developing customer applications and the designing complex operating systems comprising of both hardware and software components.

Experience

Mercury Security and Facilities Management Security Guard April 2020 - Present (11 months) Dublin, Ireland

Protex Security Systems
Security Guard
July 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months)
Dublin, Ireland

Gênio Azul General Coordinator April 2017 - April 2019 (2 years 1 month) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Coordinate school unit (Team with more than 10 people), performing control activities and financial monitoring, cash flow, issuance of invoices, hiring professionals... Control and monitoring of teachers in their activities, creation and development of teaching materials, training of the commercial team and teachers. At certain times I was a teacher and substitute in case of absences... I have a good aptitude for the financial sector.

Software and Hardware developer to find new ways for kids to learn to code and improve their logic thinks.

GRÁFICA E EDITORA

Team Coordinator November 2016 - April 2017 (6 months) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Implementation of a management system.

Coordinate a team of 5 people, with goal establishments for input savings. Delivery of operational reports, to monitor industry metrics (Indicators). Financial control of cash flow, customer service. Quality control.

- 1- Hardware developed to account for the development time of graphic materials such as outdoor arts, banners, layers.
- 2- Hardware developed to call clients that was waiting to get service.

Guia de Palestrantes e Consultores do Ceará Sales Coordinator August 2014 - October 2016 (2 years 3 months) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Main activities: Preparation and monitoring of strategic planning; Control of accounts payable and receivable; Cash flow management; Monitoring and training of the sales team; Follow reports of visits made by sellers; Creation of commercial incentives and other activities related to function; Development and monitoring of KPIs

Autocorerobotica Partner 2014 - 2015 (1 year) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Free Time

I had E-commerce to sell electronics components, like Displays, Sensors, Gears, Motor, Board Prototypes Develop platform from Arduino and Spressif Company.

I had created too many technical videos on Youtube teaching how to get a code to run it and put it to work. as you can see on the link: https://www.youtube.com/c/AutoCoreRobotica/videos

Gagliardi Distribuidora de Lubrificantes

Senior Sales Representative July 2012 - June 2014 (2 years)

Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Main activities: Preparation of routes, aiming to improve the cost-benefit; Analysis of sales potential for each region; Distribution of goals according to the profile of customers; Preparation of training for customers; Track the profitability of each client and Creation of commercial incentives

Grupo Santander Senior Coordinator June 2009 - June 2012 (3 years 1 month) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Main activities: Control of accounting standards; Management of cash flow in the treasury; Weekly meeting with cash battery to monitor monthly objectives; Customer service; Analysis of documents for account openings and card requests; Sales of banking products

TIM Participações Sales Assistant November 2008 - April 2009 (6 months) Fortaleza, Ceará, Brazil

Fulfilment of activities with the implementation of goals, activating the ability of each seller to gain commission on plans sold. Organization of the material given and received

Education

Universidade Estácio de Sá

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General · (2011 - 2015)

Universidade de Fortaleza

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2014)